Class,
today the topic of our essay is
"Dreams."
Now, before we start writing,
I'd like to ask everyone,
what do you want to be when you grow up?
Who would like to share?
Lin Ran, you go first.
I want to be a painter when I grow up.
And why is that?
There are so many beautiful things in life.
I'm afraid I'll forget them later on,
so I want to capture them with my brush.
That's great.
Does anyone else want to share?
Actually, I have other things I want to do.
Like dressing people up beautifully.
Like what?
Like an athlete.
Winning gold medals in competitions.
Or doing makeup for others.
That's also very fun.
Very nice, very nice.
And playing video games.
I really like playing games.
Actually, I like gaming the most.
Good, good.
But, you know,
we need to focus more on what we do.
Being able to do one thing well
is already good enough.
Have a seat.
Sun Jie, your turn.
I want to be a scientist.
I want to study spaceships
and explore the universe.
Excellent.
Looks like she's determined not to see us.
Making a mountain out of a molehill.
Am I wrong?
I...
Fine, okay, okay.
Alright, alright.
Haven't you ever wondered
why she lost control?
How should I know?
Last night, we all talked about our own problems,
but we didn't listen to hers.
Yeah, we were definitely out of line.
But even if we want to apologize to her,
we still need to see her.
Maybe
we can start with her problem.
Start with her problem how?
We don't have a single clue.
There is a clue.
You just didn't care enough to notice.
Tell us, then.
Last night,
weren't you trying to swap time with her?
Yeah, and didn't she refuse?
Do you think that fits her personality?
No, it doesn't.
She rarely refuses us.
This morning,
she must've had something important to do.
Is it here?
This should be it.
Teacher Lin.
Why are you late today?
Who is this?
Probably the boss here.
Shut up!
What?
You're telling me to shut up?
No, no, no.
No, Principal.
I wasn't talking to you.
I just woke up late today.
Don't let it happen again.
Okay.
As long as you're okay.
Go to your class now.
Listen up. From now on, around outsiders,
I'll do all the talking.
I wasn't paying attention just now.
I accidentally took control of the body.
Right. We won't do it again.
Anyway,
just keep your mouths shut.
Move.
Come on, say something.
Yeah, at least say a few words.
Alright, kids.
Today, we
aren't learning any techniques.
We're having a pop quiz.
Just draw
my face.
No laughing.
Draw the face.
What is this supposed to be?
Where is the person?
Where's this person?
I don't know.
It's pretty good.
Sweetie, you draw really well.
But I want to tell you,
look here.
We can add a little blush.
Right here on the cheekbones.
And like here, around the eyes.
We can also add some shading.
Teacher!
Why do I feel like it's a bit like... putting on makeup?
That's right.
Putting on makeup
is basically drawing on a person's face, right?
Alright, for today's class,
we'll stop here for now.
But before we finish,
I have a question for you all.
Does anyone know
what I'm going to do today?
You're asking way too directly.
Yeah, even if something happened,
the kids wouldn't necessarily know.
Draw you!
Besides that?
Have a test!
Let me change the question.
Did anything special happen yesterday?
No.
Yes.
You took me to the hospital yesterday.
The hospital?
Xiao Mei, let's go.
Coming, coming!
Xiao Mei.
Where's Teacher Lin?
I don't know.
Look at my drawing of Teacher Lin.
It's really pretty.
Yeah.
But Teacher Lin is acting a bit weird today.
She seems a bit mad.
What's wrong? Did you upset her?
I don't know.
Did you notice that?
I noticed.
Notice what?
I don't know.
This might be the problem Lin Ran faced.
Hello, I'd like a single-scoop ice cream.
Sure.
About me buying you ice cream today,
you can't tell your mom, okay?
I'm not stupid.
Be good.
Do you guys think he and Lin Ran
have something going on?
Hmm.
What makes you say that?
A woman's intuition.
That actually makes some sense.
When Xiao Mei went to the hospital,
her parents definitely went too.
Maybe something happened between them then.
Like a fight?
How should I know?
No point in guessing.
I took Xiao Mei to the hospital yesterday.
Were you there too?
You don't have to do this, you know.
If you want to reject me,
you can just say it.
Reject?
Did you ask me for something?
Did you really lose your memory?
Dating.
I thought about it for a long time.
Are you willing?
It's not a matter of wanting to or not.
Then what is it?
My situation is a bit complicated.
I know we haven't interacted much.
We only got to know each other a bit at the training center.
But I think liking someone is a feeling.
And I also secretly
asked your colleagues at the training center.
You are indeed single.
You are single, right?
That is true.
But it's not...
It's not as simple as you think.
How complicated can it be?
Let me ask you this.
Do you hate me?
No.
Do you have feelings for me?
Yes.
Then there you go.
Then we can totally give it a try.
Just consider it giving each other a chance.
I need to think about it.
I'm not brushing you off.
How about tomorrow morning?
I'll give you an answer.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Yes!
You really don't remember?
So,
you've been waiting for my answer all morning?
You didn't say anything.
I thought you rejected me.
Come on, you're a grown man.
You're giving up that easily?
If I didn't come looking for you,
wouldn't you have lost your chance completely?
Are you saying
I still have a chance?
I didn't say that.
When did you divorce Xiao Mei's mother?
Who?
You and Xiao Mei's mother.
When did you get divorced?
Divorced?
Yeah.
Well...
You're not still married, are you?
Scumbag!
Here, let me take over.
Teach him a lesson!
If you think I'd be the other woman,
then you misjudge me.
Now I believe...
Uncle!
I finished it. I want another one.
No way.
You can't have any more.
If you eat more, your mom will scold me.
Go watch some cartoons by yourself for a bit.
So you're her uncle.
Yeah.
Xiao Mei is your student,
and I'm her uncle.
Her mom is my older sister.
It seems we really don't know much about each other.
Yeah, that's what I said last time.
I said we don't know much about each other.
That's true, that's true.
Then how about we spend a day
and go on a date?
A date?